# Quinn Gibson

## Full Stack Software Developer







New Zealand Citizen 022 361 8680 quinngiibson@gmail.com

#### ABOUT

After leaving hospitality in 2021, I found myself being drawn towards technology for its ability to transform lives and assist people in day to day operations. I started studying in July 2021, doing a certificate and the first year of a bachelor. During this time, I was exposed to many areas of tech and learnt that software was where my passions lie.

In March 2023, I joined Dev Academy to further my software development studies. This course is intensive and fast paced, focusing on exposing us to new technologies while working solo, in pairs, and in groups. On top of this, Dev Academy also focuses on students' human skills, for giving/receiving feedback, using a growth mindset, and effective non-violent communication.

With a background of 6 years in hospitality, all things people are very important to me. I'm passionate about ensuring satisfaction and having warm, friendly interactions, as well as building rapport with my coworkers to enhance our workplace environment.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Programming Languages - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, python, SQL, SQLite

Frameworks/libraries - React, Redux, React query, Node.js, Express.js, Vite.js

Other - REST APIs, Jest, Jasmine

## **HUMAN SKILLS**

**Effective Communicator** - This allows me to actively listen to others, understand their needs, and to address my own.

**Problem Solving** - I'm open to trying a range of solutions and not becoming disheartened if the first few don't work.

**Teamwork** - I enjoy working with others as it's an opportunity for me to learn from them, or solidify my knowledge by helping them learn.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Dev Academy March 2023 - July 2023

- In my time at Dev Academy, I worked alone, in pairs, and in groups to complete challenges and produce applications.
- This 15 week course was practical, intensive, and fast paced, which I found to be really beneficial as I learn best through hands on experience. Not only did I improve my technical skills, but this course was an opportunity for me to refine the way I interact with others.

#### The Athens Yacht Club July 2022 - March 2023

 From this hospitality job, I learnt that building great rapport with my team and seeing customers feel pleased with the service I'd provided them went hand in hand.

#### Work Gap March 2021 - July 2022

- During this time, I started my tech studies and wanted them to be my first priority.

#### Original Sin January 2020 - March 2021

 From this hospitality job, I learnt how to work alone effectively and the ability to ask for support when needed.

### **EDUCATION**

#### Dev Academy March 2023 - July 2023

- Certificate in Applied Software Development

#### Ara Institute of Canterbury July 2021 - December 2022

- Certificate in IT essentials
- Completed first year of a Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology

#### REFERENCES

Available on request